Your data should also represent the problem you're trying to solve.
你的数据应该能代表你要解决的问题
It should fit your particular use case.
要能适用于你的业务场景
You can't train a production model off of artificial data.
你不可能用虚拟数据来训练一个真实的模型
You need to use production data to ensure training data matches real-world scenarios.
你需要用真实数据来确保训练数据与真实场景是契合的
You also need to determine the success criteria
同时 你需要制定模型的成功标准
for the model which is typically based on precision,
通常是基于：精度(precision)、
recall, and the F1 score.
召回率(recall) 以及 F1 score
If you determine that your model has not met these criteria,
如果你判断模型没有达到这些标准
you'll need to go back to the data and retrain.
你需要重新审视数据　并重新训练
This could entail including more edge cases,
后续操作可能是：包括更多的极端示例
more instances of classes where the model performed poorly,
包括模型表现差的那些类别的更多示例
or clearing up any ambiguity among classes.
或者进一步澄清类别间的不同点
A confusion matrix helps you understand the precision and
混淆矩阵(confusion matrix) 可以帮助你理解模型的精度和召回率
recall of your model by counting out the true and false positives,
需要计算 正确判断例子的数量 包括 真正例 - True Positives\TP 和 真假例 - True Negatives\TN
as well as the true and false negatives.
以及 判断错误的例子数量 包括 漏判 - False Negatives\FN 和 误判 - False Positives\FP
Precision indicates how often the models correct when it predicts the positive label.
精度代表模型预测为真的所有例子里 模型正确的比例
The formula is true positives over total predicted positives.
计算公式：真正例 占 所有模型预测为真的例子 的比例 即 TP\(TP+FP)
So in this example,
所以在这个例子里
that would be 45 over 60 for a precision score of 75 percent.
精度 = 45 / (45+15) = 75%
Recall indicates how many of the true positives your model predicted.
召回率代表 对于所有实际为真的例子 你的模型能测出多少？
The formula is true positives over total actual positives.
计算公式：真正例 占 所有实际为真的例子 的比例 即 TP\(TP+FN)
So here that's 45 out of 50 for a score of 90 percent for a recall.
召回率 = 45 / (45+5) = 90%
The F1 score is essentially a combination of precision and recall.
F1 score 就是精确值和召回率的调和均值
Because there are often trade-offs and aiming for higher precision or higher recall,
因为通常需要权衡取舍 并且希望获得更高的精度或召回率
you can aim to increase the F1 score.
所以目标是提高 F1 score